告诉你吧,罗斯,她要你
Ross, she wants you.
我们只是住在同一栋公寓
We just live in the same building.
-有过任何接触? -她借过我一颗蛋
-Any contact? -She lent me an egg.
-有机会了 -真的
-You're in! -Right.
嗨,罗斯
Hey, Ross.
拜托,你得再接再厉
Come on. Get back in the game.
你和瑞秋的事没指望 你前妻是个女同志
The Rachel thing isn't happening, your ex-wife's a lesbian....
我们不想有第三回
I don't think we need a third.
抱歉,能给我们个蛋吗?整颗蛋?
Could we get an egg, still in the shell?
蛋?
An egg?
对,你拿这颗蛋去还她
Go up to her and say, "I'm returning your egg."
我们赢定了
I think it's winning.
-拜托,这太离谱了 -她会喜欢的
-It's insane. -She'll love it.
-谢谢 -谢谢,给
-Thank you. -Thank you. Here.
朋友,带着蛋去
Go with the egg, my friend.
快去
Go, go, go!
-你想会成功吗? -才怪,这简直是自杀.带蛋的男人
-Think it'll work? -No way. It's suicide.
六人行 第1季 第14集 情人节糖果
The One With The Candy Hearts
-你不能这样做 -做什么?
-You can't do this. -Do what?
-罗杰明天要带她出去 -不,菲比难道你忘了为何抛弃他?
-Roger wants to take her out. -No! Remember why you dumped him?
因为他惹人厌
Because he was creepy.
卑鄙又可怖
And mean. And frightening.
但情人节有人共渡也不差
Still, it's nice to have a date on Valentine's Day!
其他任何一夜跟他约会都无所谓
You can go out with a creep any night.
我知道我会这么做
I know I do.
-你们明晚有何节目? -明天有何节目全看今天的表现
-What are you doing tomorrow night? -That depends on how tonight goes.
-关于今晚 -你不能背叛我
-About tonight -Don't you bail on me!
我答应为她朋友带一位男伴
I said I'd bring a friend for her friend.
-我知道,但她朋友好像是个… -可怜虫,我知道
-But her friend sounds like a -Pathetic mess. I know, but....
但她是如此渴望如此脆弱
Come on. She's needy, vulnerable.
我想.
I'm thinking....
谢谢
Thanks.
你和珍妮丝之后就没约过会 你一定要去
You haven't been out with a woman since Janice. You're doing this.
-她答应了 -干得好
-She said yes. -Way to go, man!
-蛋还在?. -对
Still got the egg, huh?
我的样子如何?
How do I look?
不关我的事
I don't care.
萝拉妮来了
There's Lorraine.
切记,不准交换 你有美女相伴,我有贱货作陪
No trading. You get the pretty one, I get the mess.
乔依
Hi, Joey.
瞧你带什么人来
Well, well! Look what you brought!
真帅
Very nice.
你带谁来?
And what did you bring?
她在放外套
She's checking her coat.
我去洗掉手上的出租车味
I'm gonna wash the cab smell off of my hands.
你帮我和珍妮丝点萄葡酒和红酒
Get me a white zinfandel, and a glass of red for Janice.
珍妮丝…
Janice?
Janice!?
哦…
Oh...
… 我的…
... my...
…天哪!
...God!
是珍妮丝
Hey, it's Janice!
我得逃了,我要从窗子爬出去
Okay, I'm making a break for it!
我一直梦想与萝拉妮约会
I've been waiting for, like, forever to go out with Lorraine.
-冷静点.. -冷静?
-Just calm down. -Calm down?
你竟撮合我与在五个月内 被我甩掉两次的女人
You set me up with a woman I've dumped twice in the last five months!
别这么大声行吗?你害我紧张得…
Can you stop yelling? You're making me nervous and....
我一紧张就尿不出来
I can't go when I'm nervous.
抱歉,你说得对
I'm sorry, you're right.
拜托!快点
Come on! Do it, do it!
罗杰虽讨人厌 但与彼得卡尼相较还差得远呢
Roger was creepy, but he was nothing compared to Pete.
-谁? -爱哭鬼彼德
-Who? -Pete the Weeper.
我们每次做爱他就哭
The guy that used to cry every time we had sex?
你满足吗?
"Was it good for you?"
我每天都想为霍尔那个家伙哭
I'd take crying any day over Howard, the "I win" guy!
“我赢!我赢!”
"I win! I win!"
我和他约会两个月一次都没赢过
We went out for two months. I didn't win once.
我们怎会和这些浑蛋在一起?
How do we end up with these jerks?
我们可是良家妇女
We're some kind of magnets.
我知道我有 所以我不能戴电子表
I know I am. That's why I can't wear a digital watch.
还有啤酒?
There's more beer, right?
记得我那剃光头的朋友艾比?
You know my friend who shaves her head?
No. 不
No.
我那剃光头的朋友
I have this friend who shaves her head.
她说想要停止与恶男交往的恶性循环
She says to break the bad boyfriend cycle...
可以举行一个清理仪式
...you can do a cleansing ritual.
菲比,她是个大秃头
Pheebs, this woman is voluntarily bald.
是的
Yeah.
我们明晚可以试试看
We can do it tomorrow night.
明天情人节是绝佳的时刻
It's Valentine's Day. It's perfect.
什么仪式?
Okay, what kind of ritual?
我们可以烧掉他们送的东西
We can burn the stuff they gave us.
或者是?
Or...?
或是念经,拿着权杖裸体跳舞
Or we can chant and dance around naked with sticks.
还是烧东西好
Burning's good.
知道吗
You know...
我从儿时就能用脚趾夹起25美分
... I can pick up quarters with my toes.
是吗?真厉害
Yeah? Good for you.
硬币还是纸币?
Quarters or rolls of quarters?
对了,钱德我把照片上的你都剪掉了
By the way, I cut you out of all of my pictures.
如果需要,我有一袋你的头
So if you want, I have a bag with just your heads.
不用了
That's okay.
你可以用它们做傀儡
You could make little puppets out of them.
也可以在你的“残酷戏院”中用它们!
And you could use them in your Theater of Cruelty!
-不能这么做 -什么?不能做什么?
-We can't do that! -What? What can't you do?
能过去和你谈谈吗?
Can I talk to you for a second? Over there?
我们得先离开
We might be leaving now.
告诉我“我们”是指你和我
Tell me it's you and me "we."
她说她要在我身上涂满东西 然后舔乾净
She wants to slather my body with stuff and lick it off.
我甚至不知道涂是什么意思
I'm not even sure what slathering is!
但我绝对不想错过任何部分!
But I definitely want to be a part of it!
你不能这样待我
Okay, you cannot do this to me.
你说得对,抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
三份巧克力慕斯外带
Can we have three chocolate mousses to go?
我走了
I'm out of here.
这是我的信用卡,这一顿算我的
Here's my credit card. Dinner's on me.
我希望把她扔在你身上
I hope she throws up on you.
谢谢
Thanks.
只剩下我们
-So.... -Just us.
真是糟糕的一夜
What a crappy night!
但我还是一直欣赏
I have enjoyed the fact...
你拉链里的衣服
...that your shirt's been sticking out of your zipper.
抱歉
Excuse me.
近来可好?
How you doing?
他们是我们最要好的朋友?
So do we have the best friends, or what?
乔伊哪儿称得上是朋友,他…
Joey's not a friend. He's...
他这留下信用卡的笨蛋
...a stupid man who left us his credit card.
想再来一杯?甜点?大银幕电视?
Another drink? Dessert? A big-screen TV?
-我想再来一杯 -没问题,好女人
-I'll have a drink. -Got it. Good woman!
-拿瓶最贵的香槟来 -每人一瓶
-A bottle of overpriced champagne. -Each.
对,再每人各一瓶罗伯罗伊
That's right, each. And a rob roy.
我老早就想品尝了
I've always wanted to know.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day!
我现在就开始想念你了
Oh, I miss you already.
-你能相信会发生这种事吗? -不能
-Can you believe this happened? -No, no!
但还是发生了
And yet it did.
-再见,珍妮丝 -吻我
-Goodbye, Janice. -kiss me!
钱德,抱歉
Oh, Chandler. Sorry.
Oh, Chandler. Sorry!
-珍妮丝 -摩尼卡
-Hey, Janice. -Hi, Monica.
真是太特别了
Well, this was very special.
瑞秋,看谁来了
Rach, come see who's out here!
怎么了?天啊
What's going on? Oh, my God!
珍妮丝!Hi!
Janice! Hi!
她就要走了
Janice is gonna go away now!
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
乔伊,看谁来了
Joey! Look who it is!
很好,乔伊回来了
Good. Joey's home.
这真是太好玩了
This is so much fun!
好像是大团圆一样
This is like a reunion in the hall!
罗斯,对,跟某人打个招呼吧
Ross, there's someone I want you to say hi to.
他恰好打电话来
He happened to call.
罗斯,对,是我.你怎么会知道?
Hi, Ross. That's right, it's me! How did you know?
我是说会如果狗也有时差问题
So, if dogs experience jet lag...
因为狗的七年等于人的一年
... because of the seven dog years to one human year thing...
那么狗从纽约飞到洛杉矶
...when a dog flies from New York to Los Angeles...
损失的不是三小时,而是十天
... he doesn't just lose three hours, he loses a week and a half.
真好笑
That's funny!
他们应该马上就做饭了
They should be cooking the food soon.
oh,好的
Oh, good.
她们是谁?
Who are they?
金发的是我前妻,碰她的是她的
The blond is my ex-wife. The woman touching her is her...
密友
...close, personal friend.
-你是指她们是情人? -如果你硬要这么说的话
-They're lovers? -lf you want to put a label on it.
-我还需要知道什么? -不,就这些了
-Anything else I should know? -Nope. That's it.
对了,她怀了我的孩子
Oh, and she's pregnant with my baby.
我总是忘了这件事
I always forget that part.
Hello!
我们需要鼠尾草和沙加缅度酒
Now we need sage branches and the sacramental wine.
我只有牛至叶和佛瑞斯加
All I had is oregano and a Fresca.
那样也行
That's okay!
现在我们需要正义男子的精液
Now we need the semen of a righteous man.
菲比,如果我们有 现在就无需进行仪式了
If we had that, we wouldn't be doing the ritual in the first place.
-可以丢东西了吗? -可以了
-Can we start throwing things in? -Yeah, okay!
巴瑞的信
Okay. Barry's letters.
亚当瑞塔的四角裤
Adam Ritter's boxer shorts.
晚餐的收据
And I have the receipt from my dinner with....
-这是史考帝的裸体照片 -让我看看!
-A picture of Scotty Jared naked! -Let me see!
-他穿着毛衣 -没有
-He's wearing a sweater. -No.
-这是谁的MCl卡? -我的.咻!
-Whose MCl card is that? -Mine. Shoot!
赶紧记住号码:9,7,4….
Remember this number: Nine, seven, four....
最后这是保罗的格拉巴酒
Okay, and here we have the last of Paolo's grappa.
等等,这不是几乎纯…
Wait, isn't it almost pure
我怎能在情人节甩掉她
How can I dump this woman on Valentine's Day?
天晓得,但你在新年甩掉她
I don't know. You dumped her on New Year's.
下辈子我要当马桶刷
In my next life, I'm coming back as a toilet brush.
有趣的情人
Hello, funny valentine!
珍妮丝
Hi, just Janice.
乔伊,我们的小媒婆
Hello, Joey, our little matchmaker.
我忍不住想吻你
I could just kiss you all over, and I'm gonna.
如果你不敢,就让我来开口
If you don't do it, I will.
-你真的从纽约来的? -本来不是,我从
-So are you actually from New York? -Not originally. I'm from
-你说他们可以自己做 -我以为他们可以
-You said they'd shoot it without you. -I thought they could.
最大版都是小菜一碟 最小版当然是更简单一些了啊
The maxi-pads were a piece of cake. Mini-pads should be that much easier.
-但现在是情人节 我知道,但这是我的工作
-It's Valentine's Day. -I know, but it's my job.
我会尽量赶回来,抱歉
I'll try to get back as soon as I can.
但我大部分时间都在教科学
I'm spending most of my time teaching science...
真好笑,我又不是主修科学
...which is funny because that wasn't even my major.
真好笑
Now, that is funny!
我邀卡萝过来会很奇怪吗?
Do you think it would be too weird if I invited Carol over to join us?
因为她现在一个人,怀孕了,心情又不好
Because she's alone now. And pregnant. And sad.
-大概吧 -你确定?卡萝!
-I guess. -Are you sure? Carol!
-愿意过来坐吗? -不,我没事
-Wanna join us? -No, I'm fine.
来吧,这些人会挪过去的
Come on. These people will scooch down.
你们会挪过去的,对吧? 各位挪过去好吗,动起来
You guys will scooch, won't you? Let's try scooching! Come on!
-拜托 -谢谢
-Come on. -Thank you.
克莉丝汀,这位是卡萝 卡萝,克莉丝汀
IKristen Riggs, this is Carol Willick. Carol, Kristen.
-你好 -卡萝教六年级
-How do you do? -Carol teaches sixth grade.
克莉丝汀…
And Kristen....
IKristen does something...
最好笑的是
...that, funnily enough...
是她的工作不是她的主修
...wasn't even her major!
-谢谢你们能来 -没关系.这是我们的工作
-Thanks for coming over. -Not at all. It's pretty much our job.
这就是我们为什么戴这么酷的帽子啊
That's why we get the cool hats.
-里面有什么东西? 一些真丝四角内裤
-What do we got there? -A piece of sik boxer shorts.
问候卡
Some greeting cards.
烧焦的照片
A half-charred picture of....
这家伙的体毛比队长的还浓密
That guy's hairier than the chief!
这件事说来好笑
It's a really funny story how this happened.
我拿出垃圾桶,菲比点燃熏香
I was taking out the trash, and Phoebe was burning incense
没关系.你们不用解释
It's all right.
这不是第一件烧毁男友物品失控的事件了
This isn't the first boyfriend bonfire we've seen get out of control.
-这已是今晚的第三件 -真的?
-Third one tonight. -Really?
情人节之夜是我们最忙的时刻
Valentine's is our busiest night of the year.
下一次烧你们前男友的东西时:
Next time you're burning your ex-boyfriend's stuff:
第一,在一个通风好的地方
One, do it in a well-ventilated area.
第二,如果你们要烧衣服,小心合成纤维的
Two, if you wanna burn his clothing, stay away from synthetic fabrics.
第三,试着放掉你们的怒气 学会爱护自己啊
Three, try to let go of the anger, and learn to love yourself.
-我带了东西给你 -装上子弹了没?
-I brought you something. -ls it loaded?
心型糖果“钱德与珍尼丝,永远”
Oh, little candy hearts. "Chan and Jan Forever."
我订做的
I had them made special.
ok,珍妮丝…
Okay, Janice.
嗨,珍妮丝…
Hey, Janice.
我不该告诉你
There's no way to tell you this.
至少没有别的方法来告诉你
At least, there's no new way.
我觉得我们不会结果
I just don't think things are gonna work out.
无所谓
That's fine.
It is? 是吗?
It is?
因为我知道我们还没结束
Because I know that this isn't the end.
事实上已经结束了
You see, actually, it is.
不,还没因为你不会让它发生的
No, because you won't let that happen.
难道你还不懂?
Don't you know it yet?
你爱我,钱德.宾
You love me, Chandler Bing!
不,我不爱
Oh, no, I don't.
那么就扪心自问,我们为何总是会复合? 新年是谁邀谁?
Why do we keep ending up together? New Year's, who invited who?
-情人节是谁邀谁上床? -是我,可是…
-Valentine's, who asked who into bed? -I did, but
我是你寻找的对象
You seek me out!
你的内心深处不断呼喊着我
Something deep in your soul calls out to me like a foghorn!
珍妮丝…珍妮丝…
Janice! Janice!
你推开我,你拉回我!
You push me away, you pull me back!
你要我,你需要我
You want me. You need me.
你不能没有我.你知道
You can't live without me. And you know it.
你只是不知道你知道罢了
You just don't know you know it.
明白吗?
See?
打电话给我
Call me!
这不是真的.我没说你妈是狼人
It's not true. I never called your mother a wolverine.
你有,我发誓
You did so, I swear to
她上洗手间多久了?
How long has she been in the bathroom?
我想她不是去上洗手间,她的外套不见了
She isn't in the bathroom. Her coat's gone.
或许是太冷吧
Well, maybe it's cold in there.
或许我搞砸了九年来的第一次约会
I screwed up my first date in nine years.
-有可能 -天哪
-That could be it. -Oh, God.
知道吗,这里还是很热
You know, this is still pretty hot.
磨菇
Mushroom.
微笑
Smile.
不会每次都这样的 还是有些女人会把晚餐吃完的
They won't all be like this. Some might stay through dinner.
-抱歉,不好笑 -只是
-I'm sorry. That's not funny. -It's just....
人们老说要继续你的人生
You know the whole "get on with your life" thing?
我必须吗?
Well, do I have to?
我和这位美女坐在这儿
I'm sitting here with this cute woman...
她是那么好
...and she's perfectly nice, but that...
但就这么吹了
...that's it.
我现在又和你聊天,轻松又自在
Then I'm here talking to you, and it's easy and it's fun.
我何必…
And I don't have to....
-我懂 -你懂?
-I know. -You know?
我有个疯狂的念头
Here's a wacky thought.
我们再试一次好吗?
Let's say you and I give it another shot.
我知道你要说你是个女同志
I know what you're gonna say. You're a lesbian.
但何不暂时将它摆在一旁
But what do you say we just put that aside for now.
完全不去想它
Let's just stick a pin in it.
因为我们在一起很开心 这不容你否认
Because we're great together. You can't deny it.
我有一个适合你的戒指
I've got a ring at home that fits you.
我有无数我俩一起的照片
I've got lots of pictures with both of us in them.
最美妙的地方是,你怀着我的孩子
And best of all, you're carrying my baby.
-这样不是很完美吗? -罗斯
-I mean, how perfect is that? -Ross
虽然你一直回绝, 但我仍然想对你说,我爱你
You keep saying that, but there's something right here. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
-但是 -不要但是
-But -No "but."
你要知道,暂时拦置一旁的事
You know that thing we put over here with the pin in it?
迟早会浮现的
It's time to take the pin out.
你会找到对象的,合适的女人正在等着你
You'll find someone. The right woman is waiting for you.
你说得倒是轻松,你已找到合适的女人
It's easy for you to say. You found one already.
你只需找到爱男人的女人即可
All you need is a woman who likes men, and you'll be set.
不是她
Not her.
你们真的从一个柱子上滑下去?
So, you guys really slide down a pole?
-绝对的 -太酷了
-Absolutely. -That's so cool.
那你们怎么回上面的呢?
How do you get back up?
我们很少需要像着火一样急的往上去
Well, we rarely have to return from a fire as quickly.
你们这些小伙…
So, would you guys....
你们愿意,有时,可能…
Would you like to, sometime, maybe....
有时一起出去喝一杯
Go for a drink sometime?
当然,听起来不错
Sure, sounds good.
我们午夜下班之后,来找你们可以吗?
We get off at midnight. We'll pick you up then.
好啊,太好了
Okay. Great!
你们会开消防车过来吗?
So will you bring the truck?
还会让你们拉警铃
I'll even let you ring the bell.
再见了…晚安,再见…
-We'll see you later. -Bye! See you later!
天啊
Oh, my God!
看到没有?清理仪式奏效了
See? There you go. The cleansing worked.
没错,他们是好男人
You're right. They're nice guys!
他们是消防队员
They're firemen guys!
-你们有告诉她们你们已婚吗? -当然没有,连我女友都不知道
-Tell them you're married? -No. My girlfriend doesn't even know.